So, where's your friend?
Machi and Nobu are tailing him.
He's up ahead.
We're planning to let you negotiate with the Exorcist.
Price is no object.
But no matter what, he's gotta agree.
I understand.
My fight with Chrollo is on the line.
We'll be right back.
I should probably calm my arousal, and nothing relaxes me more than ravaging someone whom I've never even met.
No, it was perfect as always.
He's just insanely perceptive.
This is troop member four. Your replacement, as it were.
I am Kaluto. I won't explain my power, but we did find him by using it.
Ah. You look quite tasty as well.
Careful.
This one goes after anything.
Hisoka, you had better make this work.
You people are so tedious. I will, but for my own benefit.
Are you serious about fighting the boss?
Of course. Who would you prefer survive, myself or your dear Chrollo?
That's stupid. Once you finish the job here, you can die for all I care.
And if I kill Chrollo, what then?
Impossible. But if you must know, I'd hunt you down and I'd kill you.
Hmm. Sounds good to me.
Our primary objective is to obtain the Angel's Breath that Team Genthrou has monopolized.
We have to force them to transform a card. If we don't succeed, we won't have a chance to use our voucher.
And that's where Team Gon comes in, isn't it?
Mm-hmm. While they may not have the strength to win outright, they're likely to deal serious damage to a member of Team Genthrou.
If they use even one of the Angel's Breaths in their possession, our voucher will transform into an Angel's Breath. And then…
We'll only need Wild Luck Alexandrite.
And if we can just manage to buy three weeks for those kids, they'll trade the card to us and we're all set.
Correct. All right. It's time. Let's go.
I believe I told you to come alone, didn't I?
We couldn't make a unanimous decision. So we all disgusted on our way over here. And now, we've finally reached a consensus.
Oh?
We choose battle!
Right! Let me on!
Accompany on! To Antokiba!
Huh?
And Book? Check your cards.
Book!
It's okay. They just got some trash for my free slots.
Same on my end.
Nothing important's missing.
That settles it. We'll kill them, yeah?
They'll put up a fight.
Huh?
I don't know what just happened, but…
Their resolve was written all over their faces.
Six copies of a company, 24 of Return, nine of Drawbridge, and two of Magnetic Force.
I spent all the money I had on them.
Right. Meet in three days. You can use that time to earn some more money and buy all the cards we need.
Right. You got it.
Do you think they'll try to come after us?
Not right away. We now have nearly twice the number of accompany cards as Genthru and his team have.
Yeah, and what if they use Clairvoyant Snake? They'll find out what we're holding.
Just watch Genthru. This is how a single star hunter fights.
Genthru.
Too slow. Don't stop to think after I grab you by the arm. React as soon as you feel a touch.
Too slow.
You're still too slow.
Now, let's take a ten minute break before we start emitter training.
He's building up his stamina. But in the two weeks we have left, I can only help him bolster his defense.
We need another weapon before we're ready to fight.
Emission training level two. Loading hand. Hold this stance by releasing aura and stay perfectly still.
See? You'll pass whenever you can launch yourself as high as I just did.
Okay!
Ha!
That looks hard. I mean really hard considering that it's just one level higher.
Of course it's hard. It's actually a level five exercise.
Wait. Are you sure it's okay to skip levels like that?
It's a gamble. If it doesn't work, the three weeks we've been given will be a waste.
If we followed the proper steps, he could reach level three quite easily.
But it wouldn't do him very much good in actual combat.
He needs an emitter type attack that can push an opponent back several meters with a direct hit.
If it's to be an effective weapon, it has to be at least that strong.
So that's level five, huh? But even if he does clear the training, being able to send your enemies flying isn't lethal.
That's exactly right. The only purpose of training at this level is to give him more options to draw on.
So, have you come up with a strategy?
Yeah, but would you mind telling me what your ability is? Then make it a whole lot easier to plan it all out.
Allow me to introduce my ability.
Cookie, the magical masseuse.
Her various massage techniques are caresses of pure bliss.
They melt away fat deposits and leave you feeling heavenly.
Aura is transmuted into special lotion, smoothing and rejuvenating your skin.
Her shiatsu makes you beautiful from the inside out, relieving constipation, stiff muscles, chills, anything that ails you.
And is that it?
No, of course not. She does chiropractic, Swedish, and deep tissue massage too. And that's only the beginning.
What are you, an idiot? That crap is completely worthless!
You're crazy! It's obviously the most useful power in the world!
You're such a stupid old...
I'm very angry!
Return on! To Zafrabi!
Hey, wait!
Was it them again?
The bastards. Their attacks are getting pretty damn brazen.
They're targeting us. There's no doubt about it.
That isn't the issue here. The issue is how they always know right where to find us.
If they used a company or magnetic force, we'd know. But that's not the case.
They're using hit-and-run tactics, then making clean escapes.
We move to a different location, but then... there they are every time.
That must be someone's ability. If they aren't using a spell for homing or tracking,
the only other explanation I can come up with is that one of their members has a Nen ability that's similar to Radar.
But we can't defend against that!
What do we do?
We'll just have to resort to drastic measures.
Nice! One copy of a company.
Alright then. Take all his C-rank cards.
Yeah, you got it. We'll set Peek on his binder.
So he hasn't met them.
It looks like he's totally clean.
Listen up. Have you heard of the bombers?
Yes. I've heard rumors.
We're the bombers.
And I just set a bomb on you.
I can kill you anywhere and at any time.
If you don't want to die, you'll bring me all the cards I request.
Hey, we just scored another accompany.
Great. I'll set Peek in here.
Damn it! This sucks!
Busted!
This is bad.
What the hell are those bastards thinking?
They're staking out the spell card shop.
And they've been attacking every player who walks out with newly purchased cards.
Now, this is just speculation.
But I think they might just be aware of me.
They've definitely realized that someone's been providing cards to Team Tezgera.
To find me, they're checking the binders of anyone who leaves the shop.
And if they find anyone who's met you in person, there's no discussion.
They're killed on the spot.
They've also been stealing all of their cards.
It seems they're totally focused on obtaining a company of Magnetic Force.
And any players who were fully cleared of suspicion and released
are then forced to collect cards for them.
By eliminating suspects and taking their cards,
they've effectively cut off our supply.
They're killing three birds with one stone.
Understood.
We'll try and keep track of their movements from here.
Get away from there now and wait for us to contact you.
They don't appear to be leaving Masadora.
Okay, so next we'll check on their cards.
It looks like the three of them have sixteen accompanies and two Magnetic Forces.
They've gained a lot.
At this rate, they'll be caught up with us in just four or five days.
But that's just about what we expected.
They don't plan to move on until they're absolutely positive that they have enough cards.
Twelve days left. We're right on schedule.
I just can't do it.
When training, visualize yourself firing a water pistol.
Gather your aura, then shoot it all out of your palm at once.
The greater the force you're able to summon, the more striking power the emitted aura will have.
Open up the nodes in your hand and emit the aura.
The amount of refined aura that you apply, the speed and the power, oh yes, and timing.
All of these elements must be present, or else you won't get the effect you're looking for.
It's too hard! I get all the other stuff from before, but not how you push it out of your hand!
He hasn't made any progress for ten days.
Maybe you should have allowed him to pick it up from level two after all.
We still have ten more days.
Yeah, only if Team Tezgera can deliver.
Looking back on it now, it wasn't a very good deal for us.
If we hand over Wild Luck Alexandrite, they're only gonna be missing two cards.
We still need over thirty, and that's gonna take us a while.
We can just take them from Genthru by force. It's not a problem.
Gon would never accept that.
Besides, we still have to figure out how to beat Genthru first.
Yes, that's true.
So, do you think this is big enough?
Yeah.
We now have forty-eight copies of A Company.
If you add up all their A Company, Return, and Magnetic Force cards, they only have forty-five.
They can't shake us now.
So I suggest we start a game of tag we can't lose.
A Company on Tezgera!
They're on the way! And their speed is unbelievable!
Stick to the plan!
Be-
A Company on, to Masadora!
A Company on, Tezgera!
Be-
A Company on, to Sophoreabi!
A Company on, Tezgera!
Amy Engineering
Accompany on, to Masadora!
Accompany on, Tuscara!
I'm all out.
Barry!
Roger!
Accompany on, to Zoframi!
Damn!
We've only got five days left!
Don't you have a little bit of advice that might help him to break through?
The sensation of Aura flowing through the body is similar but different for everyone.
All I can do is try to give him advice from my own perspective,
but he might make the wrong assumptions, you know.
Damn it!
How many left?
Seven copies of Accompany.
They're not coming. You think they gave up?
No way.
They're just taking their time to throw us off.
If we run out of a company, we have return.
Then we'll alternate between Ai-Ai and Zoframi.
How is it over there?
Let's find out.
And contact on, Gorenu.
It's Tezgera. How's it going?
Looks like you were right.
Sub and Barra showed up.
Most likely the real ones.
They might be speculating that I'll try to buy cards while they're off playing tag.
That means that the ones who are chasing you are Genthru and a couple of fakes.
It sounds like your predictions were pretty accurate.
That same trick won't work again.
There are four of us and Genthru's all by himself.
If you ask me, now's our chance.
Not yet.
I'd prefer much better odds before we fight them.
We'll stick to the plan.
Here they come. We're back on.
Goren.
Your time's up.
Training's over.
But we still have five days.
Had a change in plans.
We formed a new strategy to defeat them.
Yeah, but...
Hold on!
See, the thing is...
I think I'm getting really close.
Maybe...
Not happening.
I can't base our whole strategy on a new technique that isn't reliable yet.
Just give up.
Okay.
So the plan is...
To use this card.
You'll have to learn it the hard way.
Practice till you've got it perfect.
We're out of accompanies!
Use return!
Return on!
To I.I.
They're out of accompanies, are they?
Endgame's almost upon us.
Sub, Bara.
Have you caught anyone?
Yeah, but just one.
And it was a newbie, so he was pretty inexperienced.
Word got out that the bombers are hunting players.
So everyone's staying clear.
Well, what do you think?
Could he have been someone we've already killed?
Perhaps.
All right, just come back when you're ready.
I'm in so frobby right now.
It seems they've run out of ammunition.
We're on our last card.
If they try to follow us outside the game, we can just hole up at the mansion.
And if they don't follow us, we just have to run out the clock.
This is perfect.
Let's pick the cards we'll keep once we win.
Before we do, we should ask Mr. Batera which ones he wants.
All right, let's go.
Leave on!
Nobody's in here.
Wait, what's going on?
There were supposed to be armed guards!
Where are you?
Speak up!
Hey, Sabazushi!
Answer me!
Keep it down.
Some of us were trying to catch a nap here.
You were sleeping?
What the hell happened to everyone else?
Oh, they all left.
Huh?
Mr. Batera scrapped the whole thing.
We received a cancellation fee and an intermediary fee.
But I stuck around to let you know.
It was cancelled?
Mr. Batera, what is the meaning of this?
We've come so far.
We've almost beaten the game.
It doesn't matter.
Not anymore.
Ugh!
Doesn't matter?
What is that?
What about all the time and effort we spent?
My lawyers have been instructed to pay you.
As for the cards, do with them as you wish.
So now, please.
I just want to be left alone, I beg you.
Ugh!
Damn it!
You find out what's happening?
No idea.
But I'm determined to find out.
Ugh!
We can kill all we want out here.
Since we won't lose any ring data.
Huh?
Team Tezgera has given Gone and his friends the time they'd promised.
But waiting for them was a situation they did not expect.
We can kill all we want out here.
Put all we want out here.
was
is
the
same
yeah
uh
向かい風としていながら それでも進む理由がある
だから友よ 置いてくためだけに生きるのはまだ
早いだろ 身につけたもの 抱え込んだもの
手放したとき 始まる何か
上手く生きてく レシピを破り捨てて 感じるリズム
そう僕らのやり方で
こんにちは
それかによう
advertisements